<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reverse on Cyberrzzerk</title>
    <link>https://crazy-killer0.github.io/Portfolio//tags/reverse/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reverse on Cyberrzzerk</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Imad</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://crazy-killer0.github.io/Portfolio//tags/reverse/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>FCSC 2024 - Fifty Shades of White - Reverse</title>
      <link>https://crazy-killer0.github.io/Portfolio//posts/fcsc-2024-fifty-shades-of-white-reverse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crazy-killer0.github.io/Portfolio//posts/fcsc-2024-fifty-shades-of-white-reverse/</guid>
      <description>Introduction You are now Jesse Pinkman. You&amp;rsquo;re currently on the outs with Walter White and want to do something nasty to him.
You are asked to write a keygen for the binary that Walter has designed to restrict access to his &amp;ldquo;professional&amp;rdquo; data. The flag will appear after 50 successive validations.
We are provided with a binary and a txt file.
The chall remote then asks us to validate 50 users, so we&amp;rsquo;ll need to find a way to reverse validate() correctly in order to generate a valid serial for each user.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RITSEC CTF 2023 - Full</title>
      <link>https://crazy-killer0.github.io/Portfolio//posts/ritsec-ctf-2023-full/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crazy-killer0.github.io/Portfolio//posts/ritsec-ctf-2023-full/</guid>
      <description>redonne moi cette page markdown mais quand il y a du texte traduit en anglais:
info : https://ctftime.org/event/1860
Challenge completed Crypto Either or Neither nor A Fine Cipher Misc New Hire Wild Stocks Connection Terminated Forensics Red Team Activity 1 Red Team Activity 2 Red Team Activity 3 Red Team Activity 4 Steganography Weird turtle QR Web Echoes Rick Roll Pickle Store X-Men Lore Broken Bot Reversing Cats At Play Guess the Password Chandi Bot Chandi bot 1 Chandi bot 2 Chandi bot 3 Chandi bot 4 Chandi bot 5 Chandi bot 6 Write-ups Crypto Either or Neither nor The flag format is &amp;ldquo;MetaCTF{*}&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
